Experience a time you'll never forget.
A Time to Kill is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Joel Schumacher.
A young lawyer defends a black man accused of murdering two white men who
raped his 10-year-old daughter, sparking a rebirth of the KKK.
Jake Brigance, played by Matthew McConaughey.
Ellen Roark, played by Sandra Bullock.
Carl Lee Hailey, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Rufus Buckley, played by Kevin Spacey.
Carla Brigance, played by Ashley Judd.
Lucien Wilbanks, played by Donald Sutherland.
A Time to Kill is a 1996 American legal drama film based on
John Grisham's 1989 novel of the same name.
Sandra Bullock, Samuel L.
Jackson, Matthew McConaughey, and Kevin Spacey star, with Donald and Kiefer Sutherland
appearing in supporting roles and Octavia Spencer in her film debut.
The film received mixed reviews but was a commercial
success, making $152 million worldwide.
It is the second of two films based on Grisham's novels directed by Joel
Schumacher, with the other being The Client released two years prior.
It marked the final film appearance of Joe Seneca.
The film explores themes of sniper, rape, court, jurors, ku klux klan.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.